// Quiz Questions
var questions = [
    {
        question: "Under which HTML tag can you write the Javascript code?",
        choices: ["<javascript>", "<script>", "<js>", "<script>"],
        answer: "<script>"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax to display 'Hello World' in an alert box using Javascript?",
        choices: ["alert('Hello World')", "prompt('Hello World')", "alertbox('Hello World')", "alertuser('Hello World')"],
        answer: "alert('Hello World')"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is true about Javascript?",
        choices: ["Javascript is an object-oriented programming lanugage.", "Javascript is a dynamic computer programming language.", "Javascript is a scripting language.", "All of the above."],
        answer: "All of the above."
    },
    {
        question: "What is the different between '==' and '==='?",
        choices: ["They are the same.", "'==' checks for equality in values, while '===' checks for quality and value and type of variable.", "'===' is only used for Booleans.", "None of the above."],
        answer: "'==' checks for equality in values, while '===' checks for quality and value and type of variable."
    },
    {
        question: "What method should one use to create a new HTML element by the specified tagname?",
        choices: ["document.createElement()", "Node.createElement()", "create.newElement()", "create.TextNode()"],
        answer: "document.createElement()"
    },
    {
        question: "Where is the Javascript placed inside an HTML document/page?",
        choices: ["<body> and <head sections", "<meta> section", "<title> section", "<footer> section"],
        answer: "<body> and <head sections",
    },
    {
        question: "This method calls a function for each element in the array.",
        choices: ["while()", "loop()", "forEach()", "for()"],
        answer: "forEach()",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a valid Javascript variable name?",
        choices: ["2names", "FirstAndLast", "_first_and_last_names", "All of the above"],
        answer: "2names",
    },
    {
        question: "Which statement would you use to test for a specific condition?",
        choices: ["Select", "If", "Switch", "For"],
        answer: "If",
    },
    {
        question: "This method of an Array object adds and/or removes elements from an array.",
        choices: ["Reverse", "Shift", "Slice", "Splice"],
        answer: "Splice",
    },
    {
        question: "What does the 'this' keyword mean in Javascript?",
        choices: ["Refers current object", "Refers previous object", "Variable which contains a value", "None of the above"],
        answer: "Refers current object",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the output of console.log(2 + 5 + '8')?",
        choices: ["258", "NaN", "78", "Error"],
        answer: "258",
    },
    {
        question: "How does a FOR loop start?",
        choices: ["for (i = 0; i <= 5; i++)", "for (i <= 5; i++)", "for (i = 0; i <= 5)", "for i = 1 to 5"],
        answer: "for (i = 0; i <= 5; i++)",
    },
    {
        question: "How do you add a comment in JavaScript?",
        choices: ["<!--This is a comment-->", "/*This is a comment*/", "//This is a comment", "~This is a comment~"],
        answer: "//This is a comment",
    },
    {
        question: "What Javascript keyword declares a variable?",
        choices: ["for", "var", "if", "create"],
        answer: "var",
    }
];
